roadshow.hk 2019-06-14

# RoadShow – The Most Innovative & Influential Out of Home Media

1. | General  
  | 1.1 | RoadShow Media Group Limited (“RoadShow”) is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the Privacy Policy Statement carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding how your personal information will be treated. The Privacy Policy Statement applies to all registered and unregistered users of the RoadShow Website and may from time to time be updated, revised, reposted and changed as deemed necessary.  
  | 1.2 | By using the Website, you consent to our collection and use of your Personal Data as described in the Privacy Policy Statement.  
  | 1.3 | The following words and expressions shall have the following meaning: “Personal Data” means any identifying information or sensitive data (including but not limited to name, identity card number, gender, date of birth, contact details, occupation, e-mail address, Octopus Card number and credit card information, etc) of a person; and “Privacy Policy Statement” means this Privacy Policy Statement as amended from time to time and posted on the Website.  
  | 1.4 | In the event that there is any inconsistency between the English and the Chinese version of this Privacy Policy Statement, the English version shall prevail.  
2. | Your Privacy  
  | RoadShow respects your legal rights of privacy when collecting, storing, using and transmitting personal data and the Privacy Policy Statement explains our privacy policies and practices. It is our policy to pledge to comply with the requirements of the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance, Chapter 486 of the Laws of Hong Kong. In doing so, we will ensure compliance by our staff to the strictest standards of security and confidentiality.  
3. | Minimal Collection of Personal Data  
  | 3.1 | We collect your Personal Data when you register as a User or at times when you are requested to furnish us with your Personal Data.  
  | 3.2 | If you are under the age of 18, we recommend that you seek prior consent from your parent or guardian before providing us with any of your Personal Data.  
  | 3.3 | The purposes for which we may use your Personal Data include but are not limited to :  
  |   | (i) | to provide and download content to you;  
  |   | (ii) | to process your orders, send billing to and receive payment from you;  
  |   | (iii) | to handle and follow up your service calls, enquiries and complaints;  
  |   | (iv) | to better understand the demographics of our users and members to enable us to provide better services tailored to your needs;  
  |   | (v) | to market our products and services;  
  |   | (vi) | to verify your identity;  
  |   | (vii) | to manage your membership account (if applicable);  
  |   | (viii) | for our future marketing purposes and those of third parties; and  
  |   | (ix) | for such purposes as would enable us or our affiliates or the transferees of such Personal Data to provide website or other electronic services verification of your identity.  
4. | Disclosure  
  | 4.1 | In cases where we do collect Personal Data from you, we will :  
  |   | (i) | tell you that we are doing so and the use that we will make of such Personal Data as we collect;  
  |   | (ii) | give you the opportunity to “opt out” (i.e. to restrict the uses we will make of such Personal Data).  
  | 4.2 | We agree to take all practicable steps to keep your Personal Data confidential but we may transfer/assign such Personal Data to the following parties:  
  |   | (i) | any actual or proposed assignee, transferee or successor of our rights in respect of our users;  
  |   | (ii) | our agents, affiliates or associates where it is deemed necessary to improve our content, products and services; and  
  |   | (iii) | other companies and organisations (including advertising agencies) which may wish to provide marketing materials to you.  
  | 4.3 | Except as expressly mentioned in the Privacy Policy Statement, we will not disclose your Personal Data unless we are required to do so by law or we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to:  
  |   | (i) | comply with the laws or applicable regulations;  
  |   | (ii) | protect and defend our rights and property;；  
  |   | (iii) | protect against misuses or unauthorised use of the Website; or  
  |   | (iv) | protect the personal safety or property of our users or members or the public.  
5. | Links to Other Websites  
  | The Privacy Policy Statement only applies to the Website. If you click on any hyperlink or advertisement linking to another website that is provided on the Website, you will leave the Website for another location. At any other website, the protection of your privacy, personal data and your exposure to cookies are not our responsibility and you are advised to refer to the privacy policy of that other location (if any).  
6. | Web Logs  
  | When you visit the Website, our server may record the domain name of your computer and may also track the web pages you have visited. Such recordings and tracings are conducted for the purpose of measuring the traffic, and to gauge the popularity of various parts of the Website so that we can obtain general knowledge of our visitors. Such traffic data is collected for RoadShow’s internal use and for sharing with our content providers. We may also share the summarised data with advertisers for the promotion of the Website. Use of traffic data will not identify you as an individual.  
7. | Security  
  | Once we have collected your Personal Data, it will be maintained securely in our system. Your Personal Data, however stored, will be accessed only by our employees or contractors who are authorised to do so. Where Personal Data is stored electronically in an independent server, it will be password-protected (or under some equivalent form of protection) and accessible only by authorised personnel of RoadShow or our contractors. Employees and contractors designated to handle Personal Data will be instructed to do so only in accordance with the Privacy Policy Statement. We shall take every step to ensure that your Personal Data is properly protected. However, given the nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee absolute security. We accept no responsibility for any such unauthorised access and if you are concerned about such unauthorised access you should not provide us with your Personal Data.  
8. | Use of Personal Data in Legal Proceedings  
  | If it becomes necessary to take action against you for any reason whatsoever including recovering from you any money you owe us, you expressly agree that the Personal Data provided by you can be relied upon in identifying and taking legal action against you.  
9. | Your Rights to Access and Retention  
  | You may at any time request access to correct and update Personal Data relating to you in any of our records. You may also ask us to delete you from any active mailing or distribution list kept by us. To exercise any of your aforesaid rights, you should write to us at the address below with the envelope marked “Confidential”. In response, we may ask you to provide certain details about yourself so that we can be sure you are the person to whom the Personal Data refers.  
10. | How to Contact Us  
  | If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy Statement, please contact us at: RoadShow Media Group Limited, Flat D, 2/F, HK Spinners Industrial Building, Phase 5, 760-762 Cheung Sha Wan Road, Kowloon, Hong Kong.
